<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>


    <string-array name="bloodgroup">
        <item>not selected</item>
        <item>A+ve</item>
        <item>A-ve</item>
        <item>B+ve</item>
        <item>B-ve</item>
        <item>AB+ve</item>
        <item>AB-ve</item>
        <item>O+ve</item>
        <item>O-ve</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="picture_view_mode">
        <item>Picture + Text</item>
        <item>Picture only</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="grid_size">
        <item>3</item>
        <item>9</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="endString"> </string>

    <string name="about_jellow">
        <![CDATA[
        <head>
            <style>
                    li,p,font  {    font-size: 100%; }
                    ul { padding-left:20px; }
            </style>
        </head>
        <body bgcolor="#F7F3C6">

<p><strong>&nbsp;General Information</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Jellow is a communicator using icons to enable speech and can be used by those learning to speak or those who have difficulty with speech.</li><br/>
<li>It is developed at IDC School of Design at the Indian Institute of Technology Bombay located in Mumbai.</li><br/>
<li>A novel Visual Emotional Language Protocol or VELP was conceived and developed by the project investigators in order to enhance the language ability of Jellow. VELP represents the 6 expressive icons that form the core of the interface.</li><br/>
<li>Using these core icons, the child can communicate their likes, dislikes, and needs with others.</li><br/>
<li>Jellow is conceived as children-friendly with an easy-to-learn interface.</li><br/>
<li>The application is optimized for Android tablets.</li><br/>
<li>Jellow is currently available in English and Hindi.</li><br/>
</ul>

</ul>
<p><strong>&nbsp;Software Version: 5.0</strong></p>

<ul>
<li>The current version of Jellow is 5.0. The application is under further development. Therefore, if you have any suggestions for us, please submit it under the feedback tab.</li><br/>
</ul>

<p><strong>&nbsp;Terms of Use</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Jellow is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution Non-commercial Share Alike 4.0 International License.</li><br/>
<li>Work on Jellow is attributed to the Indian Institute of Technology Bombay.</li><br/>
<li>The content in this application comprising icons, layout, architecture, visual identity, translation, and the software codes can be shared and adopted but cannot be used for commercial purposes.</li><br/>
<li>When the content is used, we request you to acknowledge Indian Institute of Technology Bombay.</li><br/>
<li>Jellow is available for download at <a href="http://www.dsource.in/tool/jellow">www.dsource.in/tool/jellow</a></li><br/>
<li>If interested in further developing the code, please write to Professor Ravi Poovaiah at <span style="color: #ff6600;"><a href="mailto:ravi@iitb.ac.in">ravi@iitb.ac.in</a></span></li><br/>
</ul>

<p><strong>&nbsp;Credits:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Idea Conception, Project Investigation and Supervision:</strong></li>
<font>Prof. Ravi Poovaiah and Dr. Ajanta Sen</font>
</ul>

<ul>
<li><strong>Initial Concept Development :</strong></li>
<font>Anchal Kumar, Samraat Sardesai, Peter Joseph, Antara Hazarika</font>
</ul>

<ul>
<li><strong>Software Development: </strong></li>
<font>Narayana Reddy, Rahul Rupchand Jidge, Sumeet Agrawal, Roop Sahoo, Shruti Gupta, Aastha Joshi, Dhairya Dand, Pritam Pebam</font>
</ul>

<ul>
<li><strong>Website Design:</strong></li>
<font>Prof. Ravi Poovaiah, Yogesh Masaye, Sumedh Garud, Roop Sahoo</font>
</ul>

<ul>
<li><strong>Icons and Visual Design:</strong></li>
<font>Vinaya Tawde, Anisha Malhotra, Nikita Iyer, Ganesh Gajjela</font>
</ul>

<ul>
<li><strong>Translation:</strong></li>
<font>Sachin Sonawane, Dr. Sudha Srinivasan</font>
</ul>

<ul>
<li><strong>Research, Vocabulary Development, and User Studies:</strong></li>
<font>Dr. Sudha Srinivasan</font>
</ul>

<ul>
<li><strong>Support:</strong></li>
<font>E-kalpa project sponsored under NMEICT by MHRD and Microsoft Design Expo 2004</font>
</ul>
</body>
]]>
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
</resources>